# Deep Kidiya Front End Developer

#### Profile

Entry-level front-end developer with 1+ years of experience in maintaining and building web pages. Have good knowledge in designing UI applications and integration of highly transitional and scalable websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap5, and React.js. Seeking for new opportunities and challenges that will expand my skill set.



#### Professional Experience

**HTML CSS Developer** Nov 2021 - present Gandhidham Freelance

- Managed freelance projects from initial design through completion.
- Designed multiple websites for clients and portfolio

**Graphic Designer** Sep 2020 - Oct 2021 Two Digit Studio Gandhidham

- Created marketing graphics for client
- Designed several logos based on clients' needs
- Creative website designing for the company's own product.

### Education

ITI in Multimedia Graphics Jul 2019 - Jul 2020 ITI Anjar Polytechnic Anjar



HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript Bootstrap5 React.js CorelDraw Adobe Xd Figma



- Gaming - Travelling - Music

## Languages

- Hindi - Gujarati - English